Austin Howard

Morristown, TN 37813 cnfishead@gmail.com 423-353-5034

Proactive junior software developer with a passion for code and solid background of superior performance in related roles. Demonstrating 4+ years of self-taught knowledge as well as professional development at defined institutions.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Unloader/Loader

Walmart DC - Midway, TN May 2016 to December 2020

May 2016 to Dec 2020

- Used ladders and pallet jacks to load and unload merchandise weighing up to 5000 pounds.
- Labeled packages and pallets to ensure efficient identification of items.
- Operated forklifts, lift gates and pallet jacks with focus on safety and efficiency.

Shift Manager

Shift Manager

McDonalds Corp - Clarksville, TN October 2013 to May 2015

Positioned staff in key areas throughout shift to Optimize department productivity.

- Enhanced operations and boosted efficiency through employee training, coaching, and creating work schedules and assignments.
- Upheld company standards and compliance requirements for operations and cleanliness of all areas.
- Cross-trained in every store role to maximize operational knowledge.
- Established ambitious goals for employees to promote achievement and surpass business targets.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Southern New Hampshire University - Manchester, NH Present

Associate of Arts in Mathematics

Southeast Kentucky Community and Technical College - Cumberland, KY January 2016

Associate of Science in Mathematics

Southeast Kentucky Community and Technical College - Cumberland, KY

Skills

- Certified forklift operator
- NodeJS
- Bootstrap
- · Strong math skills
- Hazardous materials knowledge
- Java programming language
- HTLM
- Communication
- · Relationship building
- Expertise in Python Programming Language
- Expertise in JavaScript
- Excel spreadsheets
- APIs
- GitHub
- CSS
- HTML5
- Software Development
- Git
- User Interface (UI)
- Express.js
- templating
- ReactJS
- JSON
- REST
- MongoDB

Links

http://cnfishead.github.io